我非常喜欢你的作品  汤姆
I just love your writing, Tom,
从《天蝎》开始
ever since Scorpio.
我觉得你写得越来越好了
I think it just gets better and better.
是吗  你还读过哪本
Oh, yeah? What else have you read?
都读过
All of them.
我觉得你的新书很精彩  《上帝之釜》
I thought the latest was brilliant, God's Cauldron.
-你读过了  -一口气读完的
- You read that? - In one sitting.
但是我们最想读的一本
But what we'd really love to read
是你那本关于安德伍德夫妇的书
is your book on the Underwoods.
那个改了  改成小说了
Well, it's changed. It's fiction now.
但原型是他们
But based on them.
人们可能会去对比
People might draw parallels.
安德伍德夫妇会喜欢吗
Would the Underwoods find it flattering?
我觉得他们不会特别喜欢
I don't think they'd be too happy with it.
你觉得会畅销吗
How do you think it'll do?
-谁知道  -我希望比《上帝之釜》要好
- Who knows? - Better than God's Cauldron, I hope.
销量不高  是吗
Sales were disappointing, weren't they?
事实上  你过去十年
In fact, they've been disappointing
写的每一本书销量都不高
on everything you've written the past ten years.
我们可以用这本新书来扭转局面
We can change that with this new book.
我可不是政治工具
I'm not a political tool.
我们不是因为我妻子是你粉丝才把你接来的
We didn't fly you up here because my wife's a fan.
你肯定知道有我们想要什么
I'm sure you had a notion of what we're after.
我什么想法都没有
I didn't have any expectations.
我来是出于好奇
I just came because I was curious.
那么让我来满足你的好奇心
Well, then let me satisfy your curiosity.
如果你的书能伤到安德伍德夫妇
If your book can hurt the Underwoods,
我们要让它在竞选之前出版
we want it to be published before the election,
并且要让它畅销
and we want it to be big.
戴娜·崔斯特  你认识吧
Dana Treister, do you know her?
《名利场》的编辑
The editor of Vanity Fair.
是的  她是我的密友
That's right. She's a close friend.
还有本·格兰特  波利跳的创始人
And Ben Grant, founder of Pollyhop.
我看到网络直播了
I saw the webcast.
他们没有篡改搜索结果
They don't manipulate search results,
但是  如果在《名利场》上大做广告...
but let's just say a big spread in Vanity Fair...
精彩的选节
Nice juicy excerpt,
托马斯·耶茨的深度报道  他的文学回归
profile on Thomas Yates, his literary comeback.
我们本月上了封面  但下个月就可以是你
We're on the cover this month, but... next month it could be you.
我是最民主党的民主党
I'm on the Marxist side of Democrat.
我为什么要帮助共和党
Why would I help a Republican?
你是帮你自己  汤姆
You'd be helping yourself, Tom.
如果顺便帮助了我们
And if that helps us a little bit along the way,
又有何不可呢
what's the harm in that?
俄亥俄参议员迪恩·奥斯汀
Senator Dean Austen of Ohio,
领导层竞选伙伴的首选
the leadership's top choice for running mate.
供职国会12年
Twelve years in Congress,
能帮我们搞定这个重要摇摆州
helps us with a major swing state,
立场中立  极少树敌
middle of the road, very few enemies,
他们最看重的  是全国步枪协会的老朋友
and most importantly to them, long-time friend of the NRA.
缺点是  也是个中年白人
Now his shortcomings are he's another middle-aged white guy,
平庸无趣
underwhelming, unimaginative
而且是全国步枪协会的老朋友
and a long-time friend of the NRA.
这就是我对领导层这个选择的态度
So you can see how I feel about the leadership's choice.
参议员
Senator.
我很荣幸  总统先生
I'm honored, Mr. President.
我只有一个很大的顾虑
I just have one major reservation.
-克莱尔  -是的  先生
- Claire. - Yes, sir.
我只跟你说
Well, between you and me,
我都不确定这项枪支法案能否通过
I'm not even sure this gun bill is gonna pass.
但如果要求我支持它
But if I'm being asked to support it,
我很难做...
you know the sort of hot water--
是的  但是我需要你作为竞选伙伴
Yes, but I need you on the ticket
来平衡我们对待枪支的立场
to balance our stance on guns.
我们还要争取共和党的支持
We have to appeal to the Republicans as well.
我不要求你支持法案
And look, I'm not asking you to get behind the bill,
只要不公然反对它就好
just not to publicly trash it.
我知道这对您很重要
I know this is an important issue to you.
确实很重要
It is important,
但不如一名经验丰富
but not as much as an experienced
能拿下俄亥俄的领导人重要
leader who can deliver Ohio.
那么我同意了  先生
Then consider me on board, sir.
我们不确定能在竞选前进入投票
We're not sure we can get this to the floor before the election.
我们有言在先
That's the deal we made.
奥斯汀的事如你们的愿  法案的事如我们的愿
You get Austen, we get the gun bill.
我们首先需要一份强势的参议院版本
We need a strong Senate version first,
这样才能避免两部无力的法案相互调和
so we don't have two weak bills going into reconciliation.
你们想要奥斯汀  就要让法案通过
You want Austen, you will make this bill a reality.
或者  我们可以重新考虑竞选伙伴的人选
Or, we can revisit the choice for running mate.
别  让我们想想办法吧
No... let us see what we can do.
我打给米切尔
I'll call Mitchell.
各位
Gentlemen,
有请未来的副总统
the future vice president.
-恭喜  迪恩  -非常感谢
- Congratulations, Dean. - Thank you very much.
-欢迎  -谢谢  安德伍德夫人
- Welcome. - Thank you. Mrs. Underwood.
-认识你很高兴  -我也是
- Nice to meet you. - Very nice to meet you.
你们这边怎么样了
So, how's it going in here?
我们算是达成共识了  是吧
Well, I think we're in alignment. Wouldn't you say?
这次会面很有成效
It's been a productive meeting.
来谈谈什么时候宣布吧
So, let's talk about when we should announce.
正式宣布之前  我得安抚一下
I, uh, I need to soften the blow to the NRA
全国步枪协会那边
before we go public.
一定要保守秘密
It's imperative we keep a lid on this.
决不能提前泄露
No leaks until we're ready.
只有我们四个知情
Just the four of us in this room.
当然还有克莱尔
And Claire, of course.
我有个简单采访要做
Well, I need to go do this quick interview.
米切尔那边的进展回头通知我
Um, let me know how it goes with Mitchell.
好了  你肯定有
All right, I'm sure you have some--
开着吧  屋里太憋了
Oh, leave that open. It gets so stuffy in here.
来讨论一下时间吧
Let's discuss the timing.
是你还是第一夫人的主意
Was it you or the First Lady?
-完全是第一夫人  -她觉得可以把我争取过去
- First Lady all the way. - She thinks she can win me over?
她知道你下手肯定最重
She knows you'll hit harder than anyone else.
如果她能坚持到最后  那法案或许就能成
If she's still standing by the end, maybe the bill has sea legs.
-凯特  -早上好  安德伍德夫人
- Kate. - Good morning, Mrs. Underwood.
我们去罗斯福室谈吧
How about we talk in the Roosevelt Room?
国会的态度已经摇摆不定了
Support in the House is already wavering.
公众对枪的兴趣也在减少
The public's losing interest in guns.
不等坐下再谈吗
Don't you want to wait until we sit down?
我只有一小时的时间  得充分利用
Your staff only scheduled an hour. I want to make the most of it.
被占了
Oh, it's being used.
换个地方吧
Let's find somewhere else.
凯特
Kate?
纵观历史  枪支改革的呼声潮起潮落
Well, historically, gun reform comes and goes in waves,
你也知道  我认为这次真的会不一样
as you know, so I believe this time, it can be truly different.
数据全部在这里进行过滤
All the data's filtered here, within these walls.
分析师先初步过滤  最终
My analysts do a first pass, but ultimately,
由我做最后的筛选
I do the final round myself.
我们最关心的是安全问题
Our biggest concern is security.
顶级防火墙  跟国安局总部的一样
Top-grade firewall, same as you guys use at NSA headquarters.
内部安全呢
What about internal security?
只有我一个有全部权限
I'm the only one with full access.
你要是真发现了什么
So, if you do find anything,
怎么安全地转达给我们呢
how do you communicate that to us in a secure way?
亲自
In person.
我亲自去米德堡  或是你过来
I'll come to Fort Meade myself, or you come here.
耻辱
设备不带出去
No hardware leaves the premises.
能讲讲你们的过滤算法吗
Can you walk us through how the filtering algorithms work?
拿枪支为例吧
We'll take firearms, for instance.
从每个合法持有枪支的公民开始
If we start with everyone who legally owns a gun,
通过手机追踪用户的地理规律
track geo-location patterns through their phones,
然后描绘一张
we start to put together a portrait
持有者生活  吃饭  购物  等等的地图
of where gun-owners live, eat, shop, everything.
根据这张图  我们预测未登记
From this, we predict everyone who might want a firearm,
但有意向持枪的公民
but who isn't registered.
他们的行为模式很可能与合法持有者类似
They're likely to exhibit the same behavior as people who are.
这可以套用于对阿拉伯语感兴趣的人
You can use that for people who are interested in Arabic,
想去中东的人
uh, wanna travel to the Middle East,
或是对美国政府绝望的人
who are disillusioned with the U.S. Government...
跟我们全球监控
So the same techniques that
用的技术差不多
we're using for our international surveillance.
对
Yes...
但先进得多
but far more advanced.
好了  转过来一点  康威夫人
Okay, turn a little bit towards me, Mrs. Conway.
好
Right.
你真美  汉娜
You look great, Hannah.
-那候选人呢  -别逼我吐槽  威尔
- What about the candidate? - Don't get me started, Will.
-你真上镜  -我知道
- You're really photogenic. - I know.
弗兰妮·华莱士  大四那年
Franny Wallace, senior year.
-完全的金鱼食谱  -这些是特意摆这儿的吗
- The all-Goldfish diet. - Did you have these put here specially?
都是最棒的  亲爱的
We roll out the platinum carpet, darling.
不知道弗兰妮现在在干什么
I wonder what Franny's up to now.
反正不是《名利场》的编辑
Hmm, not the Editor of Vanity Fair, I'll tell you that.
或是即将当上第一夫人
Or about to be the First Lady.
我们真是成绩斐然啊  不是吗
Come a long way, haven't we?
是啊  威尔和我  很感谢你这么做...
Yeah, Will and I, um... Will and I appreciate your doing this.
又不是无偿的
It's not charity.
这一期有你们俩做封面肯定会卖疯了
This issue will sell like crazy with you two on the front.
我还是觉得应该报答你
Well, I feel like I should return the favor.
让我在林肯卧室睡一晚
A night in the Lincoln Bedroom?
一篇报道
A story.
带副本来了吗
You have a copy for me?
这是一份摘要
An excerpt.
-我要整本书  -你只能拿到这个
- I need the whole book. - That's all you get.
康威也拿到了一样的东西
Conway got the same thing.
-这是个错误  汤姆  -他们来找我的
- That was a mistake, Tom. - They came to me.
但他们不能发表...除非我允许
But they don't get to publish... without my approval.
你想要什么
So what do you want?
-一次会面  -为了什么
- A meeting. - For?
你只是个传话人  道格
You're just a messenger, Doug.
你听到我的话了
You got your message.
给你一周
One week.
谢谢你请的咖啡
Thanks for the coffee.
安德伍德夫人  欢迎
Mrs. Underwood, welcome.
非常感谢您能来录制这段电话自动语音
Thank you so much for recording this robocall.
这对通过这项法案将有莫大的帮助
It'll go a long way in getting this bill passed.
谢谢你出色的工作
Well, thank you for all the extraordinary work you're doing.
我要去哪里呢
Uh, where would you like me?
萨莉会带您去我们安排好进行录音的地方
Uh, Sally will show you where we set up for the recording.
这边请  安德伍德夫人
Right this way, Mrs. Underwood.
莉安
LeAnn...
那是什么
What is that?
姓名  电话号码  邮箱地址
Names, phone numbers, emails.
25万个新目标
A quarter million fresh targets.
25万  你从哪里拿到的
A quarter million? Where'd you get this?
没写回信地址
No return address.
是我们这里掌握的名字的50倍
It's 50 times the names that we have.
是真的吗
Is it legit?
好像是  我们试着打了几通电话
Looks like it. We made sample calls.
你好  我是克莱尔·安德伍德
Hello, this is Claire Underwood.
我要坦白一件事...
I need to confess something...
一件我并不引以为豪的事
something I'm not proud to confess.
当我在医院里坐在我丈夫身旁时
When I was sitting beside my husband in the hospital...
我只考虑到我自己
all I thought about was me.
我的恐惧  一旦我失去他的痛苦
My fear. My pain if I was to lose him.
这是自私的
And it was selfish.
我没有考虑到其他人
I-- I wasn't thinking about everyone else
那些曾经历同样的恐惧和痛苦的人
who had gone through that fear and pain,
那些曾坐在我所坐的位置上
who had to sit where I was sitting
他们所爱的人被不该持有枪支的人射伤的人
because a loved one was shot by someone who shouldn't have a gun.
我感到羞愧  因为我从未对此做过什么
I'm ashamed because I've never done anything about it.
我为本可拯救的那么多生命而羞愧
I'm ashamed of how many lives we could've saved.
那么多家庭本可避免这样的痛苦
How many families we could've kept from suffering.
我们都应该感到羞愧  我们每一个人
We should all be ashamed, every one of us,
因为我们所有人都有责任
because the blood is on all of our hands,
而什么都不做就等同于扣动扳机
and doing nothing is the same as pulling a trigger.
我们得做点什么
We need to do something.
那就是  修改法律
And that means changing the law.
奥斯汀参议员办公室
Senator Austen's office.
从下午开始已经接到五百多个电话了
More than 500 since this afternoon.
单单我们区吗
From our district?
我们都算少的
We have it light.
我听说其他办公室接到一千多个电话
I'm hearing that other offices have gotten over a thousand.
奥斯汀参议员办公室  我会转达
Senator Austen's office. I will take a message.
弗兰西斯
Francis.
你真的不该这么做
You really shouldn't.
抽一根不会死的
Oh, one won't kill me.
你读完了吗
Did you finish it?
嗯
Yeah.
有一个地方吸引了我
One part really caught my eye.
"一条裂缝在他们之间蔓延开来
"A chasm opened up between them,
那是一条不到九米宽的走廊
a hallway less than ten yards wide.
但它就像有两千公里那么长
But it might as well have been a thousand miles.
这是一片布置精致的无人之地
A well-appointed no man's land
丝绒地毯和高悬的天花板隔开了两间卧房
with a plush carpet and high ceiling between two bedrooms.
卧房里住着两个世纪的鬼魂
In it were two centuries of ghosts,
之前所有的总统和第一夫人
all the Presidents and First Ladies before them.
还有他们婚姻的鬼魂
But also the ghost... of their marriage.
30年的斗争  让他们的心都死了
A thirty years' war that left them both dead inside
两人之间也是一片荒原"
and this dead space between them."
真有洞察力
He's perceptive.
简直可怕
Uncanny.
那已经不是我们了  已经变了
Well, it's not who we are. Not anymore.
就算是假的  人民还是愿意相信是真的
People will want to believe it's true even if it's false.
你觉得他想得到什么
What do you think it is he wants to accomplish?
我叫你辞职之后有一晚他来过
He came here one night, after I'd asked you to resign.
他说他很着迷
He said he was obsessed.
也许他还想接着写
Or maybe he wants back in.
你对他有感情
You felt something for him.
有那么一刻吧
Maybe for a moment.
-你呢  -没有
- Did you? - No, I don't think so.
我感觉
I felt...
我感觉他看得到我
I felt like he saw me.
我也是
Me, too.
巴恩斯先生
Mr. Barnes.
你打过电话之后  我就一直在想
I couldn't stop thinking, since you called...
佐伊的事
about Zoe.
-我想要个答复  -我也是
- I guess I want answers. - That-- That's what I want, too.
-你想知道什么  -他们有过恋情吗
- What is it you want to know? - Was there... a relationship?
她和安德伍德
With Underwood?
她17岁时  去上学之前
When she was 17, just before she went off to school...
她发现我有外遇
she found out I was having an affair.
药物公司的销售代表
Sales rep, some drug company.
是个金发妞
Blonde. You know.
这是非正式的谈话吧
This isn't, you know, on the record.
当然   你不想公开就不公开
No... No, not if you don't want it to be.
你说她发现了
You said she found out.
她给我三天时间向她妈妈坦白  不然就
She gave me three days to tell her mother, or she would...
抱歉  喝了点酒
I'm sorry, I had a few drinks.
-你告诉她了吗  -告诉了
- Did you tell her? - Yeah, I told her.
我们离婚了
We split up.
那之后佐伊就不怎么理我了
Zoe didn't talk to me much after that.
我不清楚安德伍德的事
I don't know anything about Underwood.
她肯定不会告诉我
I'm the last person she would've told.
我真希望我当初  能多尽点力
I wish I would've... made more of an effort...
跟她沟通
to reach out to her.
你在开车吗  巴恩斯先生
Are you driving, Mr. Barnes?
在
Yeah.
-我快到家了  -你该停车
- I'm almost home. - You should pull over.
你查到什么了吗
Did you find out anything?
可以告诉我的事
Anything you can tell me?
她在《先驱报》没几个朋友
She didn't have a lot of friends at the Herald.
就我的了解
Um, from what I can gather,
她就没有亲密的朋友
she didn't have any close friends at all.
我跟她邻里的人谈过
I spoke to some people in her neighborhood...
但还没什么发现
but nothing so far.
你会告诉我吗
Will you?
-如果查到  -当然
- If you... - Yeah, of course, of course.
如果你想起了什么
If you think of anything...
当然
Yeah.
枪支  阴谋和白宫
那你当时去那儿干什么
Then what were you doing there?
我去白宫开会
If I do a meeting at the White House,
还需要理由吗  茱莉亚
I don't have to explain myself, Julia.
法案可能会通过
This bill might pass.
-我知道  -你在帮他们吗
- I realize that. - Are you helping them?
当然没有
Absolutely not.
-茱莉亚  -安德伍德夫人
- Julia. - Mrs. Underwood.
抱歉  我该跟你握手  但我刚跑步回来
Sorry, I'd shake your hand, but I just got back from a run.
我想说
Listen, I wanted to say,
我知道上次的会面不太顺利
I know our meeting last time didn't go very well,
那是怪我  我的话太无礼了
and that's on me. It was rude, what I said,
希望你接受我的道歉
and I hope you'll accept my apology.
请坐吧
Have a seat, please.
你以前进过宅邸吗
You ever been in the residence before?
套近乎我也不会支持你的
The personal touch isn't going to bring me on board.
给国会打几万个电话也没用
Neither will a few thousand calls to Congress.
不到24小时  8.4万个
84,000 in less than 24 hours.
先不谈那个
But let's put that aside for a moment
-来说说你的好朋友  -谁
- and talk about your good friend. - Who?
-奥斯汀参议员  -他说了  竞选伙伴
- Senator Austen. - He told me. Running mate.
不只是竞选伙伴
Oh, not just running mate.
你说我不必支持这个法案的
You said I wouldn't have to support this bill.
是啊  但是计划赶不上变化  迪恩
Yes, but a lot can change in a day, Dean.
没想到会有这么大的呼声
We had no idea there'd be this sort of groundswell.
就因为跟你共处一室
Julia Melman was all over
茱莉亚·梅尔曼就对我逼问个不停
my ass even for being in the same room as you.
你告诉她了吗
Did you tell her?
-没办法  -天哪  迪恩
- I had to. - Christ, Dean...
不然就要树个死敌
It was that, or make an enemy for life.
她很生气  但应该能想明白
She's upset, but I think she'll come around,
除非你逼我支持
unless you make me endorse
堵上枪展和网络卖枪的漏洞
closing the gun show and Internet loopholes.
那她可就要爆发了
Then she'll go ballistic.
迪恩不会的  我们为他竞选出资上百万
Dean wouldn't do that. We've poured millions into his campaigns.
现在他不需要你了
And now he doesn't need you anymore.
你是要威胁我吗  逼我们让步
Are you trying to intimidate me? To get us to back down?
不  我有个提议
No, I have an offer.
民主党想拿下俄亥俄不容易
Ohio's a tough state for Democrats.
茱莉亚一直对我很好
Julia's been very good to me.
我懂  忠诚是很重要
Loyalty's important, I understand,
但你现在必须忠于我
but your loyalty has to be with me now.
我做不到
I just can't do it.
好吧  那就不公布了
All right, then we'll cancel the announcement.
我另找个竞选伙伴好了
I'll find someone else to be my running mate.
不  我  我没法支持这项法案
No, I mean, I... I just can't support this bill.
但是现在  两件事绑在一起了
Oh, but you see, the two go hand in hand now.
你答应不答应
So, are you on the ticket or not?
如果众议院通过  参议院不通过呢
What if the gun bill passes in the House, but not the Senate?
你要什么回报
In return for what?
你说服参议员退出
You convince the senator to pull out.
领导层想要他  我们也配合了他们
Now, the leadership wants him, and we've played nice,
但我和总统想要的是凯茜·杜兰特
but the president and I want Cathy Durant.
她参选要更有希望
She's a much stronger candidate.
你愿放弃自己的法案吗
You're willing to abandon your own bill?
要在击败康威和击败你之间选
If it's means beating Conway or beating you,
多容易选啊
that's not a hard choice.
我已经告诉迪恩
I already told Dean that
他做竞选伙伴我可以接受
I could live with him being running mate.
我怎么能反悔
How do I backtrack?
明天看新闻吧
Just watch the news tomorrow.
你做了正确的选择
You made the right choice.
-但愿吧  -别但愿  就是
- I hope so. - Well, don't hope so, know so.
我会让赛斯给你一份讲稿
And I'll have Seth send you a copy of the speech.
可以送参议员出去了  谢谢
You can show the senator out now, thank you.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
-抱歉  -没关系  进来吧
- Oh, I'm sorry. - It's okay. Come in.
-他怎么说  -愿意配合  她呢
- What did he say? - He'll do it. What did she say?
会考虑一下
That she'll think about it.
怎么知道她不会把计划说出去
How do we know she won't tell him our plans?
我说如果她说出去
I told her if she does,
我们就尽力让参议院通过法案
we'll make sure the bill goes through the Senate.
给我递条毛巾好吗
Can you hand me a towel, please?
-密查姆的手  -什么
- Meechum's hand. - What?
我前一阵在楼下一面墙上画了个轮廓
I traced it on a wall downstairs... A while back.
被粉刷盖上了  算了
They've painted over it. Oh, never mind.
弗兰西斯  我在想耶茨
Francis, I've been thinking about Yates.
康威夫妇什么都有
The Conways have everything.
有孩子  视频  推特
They have their children, their videos, their Twitter.
没几个人理解我们
There are very few people who understand us.
密查姆就是一个
Meechum... was one.
汤姆也是
Tom is another.
八
Eight...
七  很好
Seven. Nice.
长裤子先生
Mr. Long Pants.
帅鞋子先生  滚吧  滚吧
Mr. Nice Shoes. Go! Go, go, go.
-滚  -你饿吗
- Go! - Are you hungry?
不要钱  你走  带着你的钱走
No money. You need to go. You and your money, go.
-我要叫警察了  -好了  好了
- I'm calling the cops. - All right, all right.
-马上叫警察  -好了  好了
- The cops, right now... - All right, all right.
-我要叫警察  -好了  好了
- I'm calling the cops. - All right, all right.
女士
Ma'am...
我是汤姆警员
I'm Officer Tom.
是您打的电话吗
You called for me?
刚刚有个人
There was a man here.
很坏的人
A very bad man.
-您住在这街区吗  -33年了
- Do you live on this block? - Thirty-three years.
Three... three.
在这儿见过这个坏人吗
Did you ever see this bad man on your block?
好吧
All right.
那这个女人呢  见过她吗
What about this woman? Did you ever see her?
-真美  -是的  是很美
- Pretty. - Yes, yes, she is.
婊子
Whore!
-滚开  -为什么那么说
- Go away! - Why'd you say that?
-滚开  滚开  -为什么那么说  告诉我
- Go away. Go away. - Why'd you say that? Tell me.
告诉汤姆警员  为什么那么说她
Tell Officer Tom. Why did you call her that word?
滚开
Go away!
我和儿子亲手建的
Built this myself, with my son.
他明年春天爬船长峰
He's doing El Capitan next spring.
徒手攀登
Free-climb.
我觉得竞选总统
I feel like running for president
就像不系安全绳爬悬崖
is like climbing a cliff without a safety rope.
对了  媒体怎么不知道你在这儿
How is it the press don't know you're here, by the way?
像你一样  将军
Just like you, General,
我周末也会休假  陪陪家人朋友
I take Sundays off to spend time with family and friends.
或是交新朋友
Or to make new friends.
州长  我知道你还是希望我辞职
Look, Governor, I know you still want me to resign.
但我之前不该拿那个做威胁
But I was wrong to threaten that.
德雷尔告诉我哈里发国这周又占领了一块油田
Dreyer told me ICO took over another oil field this week.
他们势力在壮大
They're growing.
德雷尔什么都跟你说啊
Dreyer shares a lot with you, doesn't he?
这就发生在你眼皮底下  将军
This is happening on your watch, General.
总统不作为  你也不能逼他
The president isn't acting and you can't force him to.
只要你留下就不能
Not if you stay.
不过你要是辞职  我保证你还会有工作的
If you resign, though, I promise it'll only be temporary.
我一扯上政治  就回不了头了
Once I get political, I can't cross back over the line.
我不是要等上任后重新委任你
I don't mean a recommission.
我要你现在做我的竞选搭档
I mean making you my running mate.
谢谢
Thank you.
-读了吗  -只读了摘要  很有力
- Have you read it? - Just an excerpt. It's powerful.
会很有争议  答应我我就给你看
And it'll be controversial. Say yes and I'll show you.
《电讯报》不会允许的
The Telegraph would never let me.
-母公司都是我们家  -那也不行
- Same parent company, both our titles. - Doesn't matter.
报社对打兼职有很明确的态度
Paper is strict when it comes to moonlighting.
没关系  因为我爸爸是董事
It does matter, because my dad is on the board.
给你的编辑打个电话
One call to your editor...
会有很多人抢着要这个
There... there are plenty of people who would jump at doing this.
但没有对他那么"了解"的人
Not who know him intimately.
我的新竞选记者
My new election correspondent,
看到你和耶茨在竞选途中溜出去了
he saw you and Yates sneaking off on the campaign trail.
耶茨会对你坦言的
Yates will open up to you.
你肯定知道该怎么出招
I'm sure you know what buttons to push.
有利益冲突
It's a conflict of interest.
我爸爸给我看了你写的文章
My dad showed me that article you wrote.
你叫他暴君  没发表出来的那篇
The one that never went to print where you called him a tyrant.
有些人的职业是靠声誉打下来的
Some of us have built our careers on our reputations,
而不是靠摆弄爸爸给的杂志
not by having their daddies give them a magazine to play with.
或是跟老同学套近乎
Or by cozying up to old school chums, right?
这些话我都听过
I've heard it all before.
你可能不喜欢我  不喜欢康威夫妇
You may not like me, you may not like the Conways,
但我觉得比起让安德伍德再干四年
but I have to believe you can stomach us better
你会更愿意接受我们
than another four years of President Underwood.
-写得不错  -我知道
- Well, the writing is good. - I know.
但还不足以胁迫总统
Not good enough to strong-arm a president.
倒是能让我进到这屋里来
Well, good enough to get me in this room.
我以为弗兰西斯跟你说清楚了
I thought Francis made it very clear to you,
你不能挑衅我们
you were not to challenge us.
是啊  他说他会告诉全世界
Yeah. He said he would tell the world
《天蝎》不是我写的
I didn't write Scorpio.
我希望你明白
I hope you understand
我们不能让你在选举前出版这本书
that we can't allow you to print this before the election.
我明白
I do.
那你为什么想见我
Then why did you want to meet?
我需要个结尾
I need an ending.
我有个还凑合的结尾  但我不喜欢
I have one I can live with, but not the one I love.
-因为是假的  -你的确走了
- Because it's false. - Well, it's true that you left.
我要是走了  就不会在这儿了
If I left, I wouldn't be here.
我根本不相信
I don't believe for a second
你去拜访你母亲是因为她病了
you went to visit your mother because she was sick.
为什么
And why is that?
因为你一次都没跟我提过她
Because you never mentioned her one time to me.
有时候只字不提能代表千言万语
Saying nothing says a lot sometimes.
要是故事重点不是她如何离开
Well, what if the story isn't about how she left,
而是她如何回来呢
but how she came back.
你在这里  不代表你全身心都在
Just because you're here doesn't mean you're here.
你肯定想知道吧
Well, wouldn't you like to know?
你不是想要结尾吗
Don't you want your ending?
你要跟我说吗
Are you gonna tell me about it?
关于你们俩  不许说谎
About the two of you? No lies.
不  我什么也不说
No, I'm not going to tell you anything.
你可以像以前一样观察
You can observe, like you did before.
不过这次  你所见到的一切都属于你
The difference is everything you see this time will be yours.
我们想得到点东西作为回报
And in return, we would like something.
讲稿  我们需要了解我们
Speeches. We need someone who knows us...
也了解我们态度的人
and knows our voices.
讲稿撰稿人  你开玩笑吧
A speechwriter? You're kidding.
只有这个办法能解释你为什么和我们在一起
It's the only way to justify you being with us...
以防媒体问起
in case the press ask.
你们是想盯着我
You want to keep an eye on me.
我觉得挺公平的  你不觉得吗
Well, I think that's fair. Don't you?
如果你要盯着我们的话
If you're keeping an eye on us?
你给我们一周  我们就给你一天
So you gave us a week. We'll give you a day.
就是在这里  在这个地方
It was right here, on this very spot,
我被一支非法获得的手枪
that I was shot with two bullets
所射出的两颗子弹击中
from an illegally obtained handgun.
特勤局特工艾德华·密查姆
Secret Service Agent Edward Meechum,
他是位海军陆战队员  也是我的朋友
a marine and my friend,
因同一支手枪射出的子弹而牺牲
was slain with the bullets from that very same gun.
最近几天
The public support...
公众对第一夫人的《背景普查法案》的支持
for the First Lady's... Universal Background Check Bill
呼声震耳欲聋
has been deafening in these last few days.
我们听到了成千上万人的呼声
We have heard from thousands and thousands of voices,
今天  我们想向其中再增加一个声音
and today, we would like to add one more voice to that chorus.
这声音强而有力
And it is a powerful voice.
俄亥俄州迪恩·奥斯汀参议员
Senator Dean Austen of Ohio.
谢谢您  总统先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
我十多岁起就是全国步枪协会的成员
I've been a member of the NRA since I was a teenager.
我一直都是持枪权利的强烈支持者
I've always been a fierce advocate for gun rights.
但今天我要强力支持
But today I want to offer my strong support
第一夫人的法案
for the First Lady's bill.
给你
Here you go.
-我再问你一个问题  -我告诉你  伙计
- Let me ask you another question. - I'm tellin' you, man,
你要是说她住在这个街区  我相信你
if you say she lived on the block, I believe you.
但她肯定不喜欢披萨
But she must not have liked pizza,
因为我不记得见过她的脸
'cause I don't remember ever seein' her face.
不是她  安德伍德总统
Not her. President Underwood.
天啊  这人真是阴魂不散
Oh, Christ, I can't get away from this guy.
他妻子刚刚给我打电话了  关于枪的自动电话
His wife just called me. Robocall about guns.
你在这附近见过他吗
You ever seen him around this neighborhood?
见过  经常见到
Oh, yeah. All the time.
周五晚打过保龄球后和英国女王一起
With the Queen of England, Friday nights, after bowling.
在他还在国会的时候
When he was in Congress.
一次都没见过
Nah, never once.
否则我会记得的  我擅长记面孔
I would've remembered. I'm good with faces.
-帕尔玛干酪  -在那边
- Parmesan? - Over there.
但我见过几次这个人
I saw this guy a few times, though.
-参议员  -不  那个死掉的人
- The senator? - No, the, uh, the dead guy.
那个特勤局的
The Secret Service guy.
在这儿吗
In here?
是啊  他之前经常来喝咖啡
Yeah, a while back. He used to stop in for coffee.
不吃披萨  只喝咖啡
Never any pizza, just coffee.
-你确定吗  -我说过  我擅长记面孔
- You're positive? - Yeah. I told you, I'm good with faces.
"起落架收起了  几秒钟之后
"The wheels lifted, and within seconds,
华盛顿就消失在一团烟雾中了
Washington fell away, disappearing under a blanket of haze and smog.
她前额顶着窗户
Forehead pressed to the window,
想象一千年前
she imagined this was exactly
这里肯定也是这番景象
how it must have looked a thousand years ago,
太阳升过云端
when the sun rose above the clouds
而下面只有一片沼泽
and there was nothing but a swamp beneath.
在这个高度  看到这样的景象
From this height, with this view,
她可能是在任何地方
she could be anywhere.
但关键是  她不在那里"
But the important thing is she was anywhere but there."
终
-还要一杯吗  -要
- You want another? - Yeah.
终
他说为什么了吗
Did he say why?
谢了  戴娜
Okay, thanks, Dana.
耶茨退出了
Yates pulled out.
说他跟安德伍德夫妇达成了协议
Said he came to an agreement with the Underwoods.
他拿我们相互做筹码
He was playing us off each other.
我们还是可以放出摘要
We could still leak the excerpt.
太冒险  不被人查到还好
It's too risky. If we get away with it, great.
要是被查到
If we don't,
我们就成了坑害知名小说家的投机分子
we look like opportunists fucking over an acclaimed novelist.
不值得
It's not worth it.
你觉得他们之间真的有裂痕吗
Do you think it's true, that chasm between them?
谁知道
Who knows?
我喜欢他的文笔
I love that writing.
-真希望能看到其他部分  -我讨厌《天蝎》
- I wish I could've read the rest of it. - I hated Scorpio.
-写得多美  -就是垃圾
- It was beautiful. - It's garbage.
-为什么  -主角是个怂货
- Why? - The main character's a pussy.
-威尔  你知道我讨厌那个词  -他就是
- Will, you know I hate that word. - He is.
他最好的朋友自杀  他却袖手旁观吗
He lets his best friend kill himself. He does nothing?
他很痛苦  反正也要死了
He was in pain. He was going to die anyway.
那也不重要  还是懦弱
It doesn't matter. It's cowardly.
我觉得他很勇敢  他朋友也是
I think he was brave. And his friend.
我觉得耶茨能写出来也很勇敢
And I think Yates was brave to write it.
勇敢是不放弃  无论如何战斗到底
Brave is never giving up. You fight, no matter what.
如果耶茨同意  凯特·鲍德温也同意
So, Kate Baldwin was willing if Yates was in?
是啊  戴娜让她写两万词
Yeah, Dana was giving her 20,000 words.
应该可以再斡旋一下
I think we can pivot.
怎么做
How?
再给她打个电话
Get her back on the phone.
-茱莉亚  -奥利维亚  都不知道你来了
- Julia. - Olivia, I didn't know you were in town.
就是来看看
Oh, just a little visit.
我有时候还挺想迪恩的  别告诉他
I miss seeing Dean's face sometimes. Don't tell him that.
-能让我们单独谈吗  -她不用走
- Will you give us a few minutes? - No, she should stay.
我知道你们有事要谈
Oh, I know you have things to discuss.
比如你丈夫放弃做竞选伙伴
Like your husband withdrawing from the ticket.
她是为此而来吧  跟你一起宣布
That's why she's in town, right? For the announcement.
我知道那个新闻发布会肯定让你很意外
I know the press conference must've caught you off guard,
但总统不想让你知道
but the president didn't want you to know.
-他觉得你会组织抗议  -他说对了
- He thought you'd organize a protest. - He was right. I would've.
我希望能坐下  宣布之前好好谈谈
My plan was to sit down, talk this out before the announcement.
没什么好宣布的了
There isn't gonna be an announcement.
你不能大摇大摆走进来
You... you can't waltz in here--
你丈夫初出茅庐时
We've raised $20 million
我们就给他捐了两千万
for your husband since he was a freshman.
我就可以随时大摇大摆走进来
That gives me the right to waltz in whenever I want.
-放尊重点  -亲爱的  行了
- Show some respect. - Honey, please.
不  这是我们要的
No. This is what we wanted.
-我们奋斗的目标  -等安德伍德输了
- What we've worked for. - When Underwood loses,
你接下来两年可就有仗要打了
you'll spend the next two years fighting off a primary opponent.
我们在俄亥俄的二十万会员都会反对你
Every one of our 200,000 members in Ohio will turn on you.
等你没了这个职位
By the time you've lost this office,
奥利维亚的律所也会黄了
Olivia's law firm will go tits up.
别忘了  我们给你引了好多客户
Don't forget, we pushed most of your clients your way.
他临阵退缩了  我能怎么办
He got cold feet. What can I do?
劝他改主意
Convince him to change his mind.
他不听  他说全国步枪协会对他严词威胁
He wouldn't listen. He says the NRA came down hard on him.
因为你让上了新闻发布会
Because you had him do the press conference.
不  那是奥斯汀的主意  不是我的
No, that was Austen's idea, not mine.
我跟他说了要低调
I told him to lay low,
但他说如果他要加入  就要完全投入
but he said if he was in, he wanted to be all in.
我们的打算是平衡你们两人的立场
The idea was to balance the ticket.
奥斯汀这条路已经不通了
Well, we can't do anything about Austen.
问题是我们能找谁来代替他
The question now is who do we get to replace him?
再看看名单
Go back to the list?
他还好  但那张名单上别人我都没兴趣
He was fine, but I'm not enthused by anyone else on that list.
别又回到起点了  总统先生
Let's not go back to square one, Mr. President.
我们有个不错的名单
We have a good list.
大家都会支持那些人的
Everybody can get behind those names.
这是常理
It's common sense.
常理唯一的问题就是  太普通了
The only problem with common sense is that it's so... common.
我觉得我们有更好的选择
I think we can do better.
谁
Who?
凯茜·杜兰特
Cathy Durant.
路易斯安那不是摇摆州  这我清楚
Now, Louisiana's not a swing state, I know that.
但她仍然是个全国知名人物
But she is still a national figure,
她能帮助我们争取女性选民的选票
she helps us with the women's vote,
并且我信任她
and I trust her.
枪支呢
What about guns?
她似乎对此立场并不坚决
I don't think she's ever had a strong position.
比那更好  她对这个问题从未发表过意见
It's better than that. She's never uttered a word on the issue.
我们查过了
We checked.
-我喜欢  -我也是
- I like it. - So do I.
-但我还有个想法  -谁
- But I had another thought. - Who?
不是"谁"  是怎样
Not "Who." How.
我觉得不应该由我选她
I don't think I should choose her.
我认为应该由党选她
I think the party should choose her.
你不是说开放代表大会吧
Not an open convention.
鲍勃  我们
Look, Bob, let's...
我们必须面对事实
We have to face the fact that
我的健康状况将会对我们非常不利
my health is gonna be a major liability for us.
不论谁做竞选伙伴
No matter who becomes the running mate,
那人最终都可能成为总统
they could well end up being president.
那种情况
Now, that is a...
我甚至都不愿想
a scenario that I don't even like to fathom,
但是我们无法回避
but we can't escape it.
如果这个决定如此重要
And if it's such an important decision,
为什么不让党来决定呢
why not let the party make it?
因为那样大家都可以参选
Because it'd be a free-for-all.
不不  我们要想办法让凯茜获胜
No, no. We make it so that Cathy wins.
只是要做得像是党选择了她
We'll just make it look like the party chose her.
想想新闻报道吧  会铺天盖地的
And think of the coverage. We'll own the news.
你想把党代会变成马戏团
You want the convention to be a circus.
鲍勃  我不知道你有没有注意到
Oh, Bob, I'm not sure if you've noticed or not,
但政治已经不只是戏院了  是娱乐业
but politics is no longer just theater, it's show business.
那我们就演一出最棒的戏吧
So let's put on the best show in town.
太好了
Great.
能向我敬个礼吗  将军
Will you give me a salute, General?
现役军人不能接受媒体采访
Active military aren't allowed to speak to the press.
他今天早上辞职了
He delivered his resignation this morning.
不是吧
No shit.
只等总统同意  我们立刻就在网上发布
We're gonna break it online as soon as the president accepts it.
月刊不常得到这种首发猛料吧
Not often a monthly gets raw meat like this, huh?
他的电话会被打爆的
His phone's gonna blow up.
但你会得到独家采访
But you get the exclusive.
-汤姆的事很遗憾  -我不觉得
- Sorry about Tom. - I'm not.
谢谢你  将军
Thank you, General.
好了  我们要准备...
All right, we're gonna go set up for the...
下午好  将军  我是凯特·鲍德温
Good afternoon, General. Kate Baldwin.
我们开始吧
Shall we?
不用说  安德伍德夫人
So, the main issue that Mrs. Underwood
一直关注的主要问题是枪支
has been focusing on is guns, obviously.
我们准备了一些最近用的谈话要点
We've got some talking points we've been using,
-你想  -抱歉  有水吗
- so you'll want to... - I'm sorry, is there any water?
有
Yes.
我有点宿醉
I'm a bit hungover.
至少现在清醒了
At least I'm not still drunk.
要来点吗
Want some?
不用
Uh, we're fine.
好
Right.
那么
So...
谈话要点
to the talking points.
什么事
What is it?
几位容我失陪一下
Excuse me for a moment, gentlemen.
我最想说的  是死亡人数
What I want to communicate mostly is about the death toll,
个人经历  以及那些能打动...
with personal stories, things that connect with--
克莱尔
Claire.
-汤姆  -总统先生
- Tom. - Mr. President.
能谈谈吗
Can we speak?
那么  你们两个继续
I'll, uh... I'll leave you to it.
她真的在乎什么枪支问题吗
Does she actually give a shit about guns?
她在不在乎有什么关系
What's that got to do with anything?
我们知道会有这种可能
We knew this was a possibility.
他会闹出很大动静  肯定是康威搞的鬼
He's gonna make a lot of noise. It's Conway, I'm sure of it.
问题不在康威  而是莉安
Problem isn't Conway, it's LeAnn.
是她强力主张取消空袭的
She pressured us to cancel the air strike.
已经做出的决定  就不要多想了  道格
We chose our path, Doug. Let's not second-guess it.
请原谅  安德伍德夫人  但是她有害
No offense, Mrs. Underwood, but she's doing damage.
我认为应该踢掉她
I think we should replace her.
我们要通过枪支法案就得靠她
She's the reason we're gonna pass the gun bill.
先生  《名利场》主编戴娜·崔斯特
Sir? I just got this from Dana Treister,
刚给我发来了这个
the editor of Vanity Fair.
我不确定是什么意思
Not sure what it means...
他打算把这老混蛋定为竞选伙伴
He's gonna make that son of a bitch his running mate.
-什么情况  -我去查查这个人
- What's goin' on? - I'll see what I can dig up on him.
不  他当初担任
No. He was fully vetted
参联会主席时已经彻底审查过了
when he was commissioned for the Joint Chiefs.
你和赛斯就他的辞职起草一份声明
No, you go with Seth and draft a statement on the resignation.
-好  先生  走  -什么情况  道格
- Yes, sir. Let's go. - What's going on, Doug?
都怨莉安
And it's LeAnn's fault.
要不是她  他根本不会辞职
He never would've resigned if it wasn't for her.
你去查查
See what you can find.
将军吗  总统说不用查了
On the general? The president said we shouldn't.
去查莉安
On LeAnn.
我可不想搀和办公室政治
Hey, I don't wanna get involved in some cage match--
我们不是说过了  你得服从我
I thought we had an understanding. Your obedience.
我尽量去查
I'll see what I can do.
你同意道格吗  你对莉安有疑虑吗
Do you agree with Doug? You're having reservations about LeAnn?
对汤姆的疑虑比她要大
Less about her and more about Tom.
不过我说了相信你的判断  我就会相信你
But I told you I trust you on this, so I'm trusting you.
-领导层同意了吗  -他们有疑虑
- Has the leadership agreed yet? - They're skeptical.
我们可以利用这个
We can use this.
先生们  如果你们对
Well, gentlemen, if there was
党代会还有什么疑虑的话  放下吧
any doubt about an open convention, let it go,
因为我们必须把这则新闻盖下去
because we're gonna wanna bury this news.
布洛哈特刚刚辞职了
Brockhart has just resigned.
将军马上就要登上《名利场》的封面了
And the general is about to appear on the cover of Vanity Fair.
想想康威会怎样大加利用吧
Imagine what Conway can do with that.
康威  康威  康威
Conway! Conway! Conway!
多谢你的到来
Thank you for coming.
感谢前来支持  感谢你的支持  谢谢
Thank you for coming. Thank you! Thank you!
多谢你来支持我
Thank you for coming out.
-戴娜给我发了这个  -很高兴见到你
- Dana just sent me this. - So great to see you.
消息发布了
The story broke.
-你好  -我妻子多完美啊
- Hello. - Isn't my wife perfect?
谢谢
Thank you.
让她听听你们多喜欢她
Let her know how perfect you think she is!
别闹
Stop it.
你真讨厌
You're too much!
-谢谢  谢谢  -康威  康威  康威
- Thank you! Thank you! - Conway! Conway! Conway!
2013年11月
我知道  福斯托
Yeah, I know, Fausto.
我也是光想想都觉着累
I get exhausted just thinking about it, too.
2013年9月  2013年10月  2013年11月  2013年12月
好了
All right.
万里长征第一步
A journey of a thousand miles.
艾德华·密查姆  出行记录  13年5月1日-13年6月30日